Guide to the Mix Collection, 1970-2014 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS.143
Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES X: 1996, 118087
  - Subseries J: Grants/Fundraising/Sponsorship (see also Oversize series), 118088
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Advertising register, 1996; 118124 (Box 10, Folder 943)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Sponsorship package information, 1996; 118123 (Box 10, Folder 944)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Magazine sponsors, 1996; 118122 (Box 10, Folder 945)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Notes, week of Festival, 1996; 118121 (Box 10, Folder 946)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Correspondence (STILLS INCLUDED), 1996; 118120 (Box 10, Folder 947)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Rejected sponsors, 1996; 118119 (Box 11, Folder 948)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - HX, 1996; 118118 (Box 11, Folder 950)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - PlanetOut, 1996; 118117 (Box 11, Folder 951)
    - Advertising/sponsorship - Village Voice, 1996; 118116 (Box 11, Folder 952)
    - Grants/fundraising - Grant writing notes, 1996; 118115 (Box 11, Folder 953)
    - Grants/fundraising - Grant proposal narrative drafts, 1996; 118114 (Box 11, Folder 954)
    - Grants/fundraising - misc. grant documents, 1996; 118113 (Box 11, Folder 955)
    - Grants/fundraising - A Different Take grant proposal, 1996; 118112 (Box 11, Folder 957)
    - Grants/fundraising - Astraea, 1996; 118111 (Box 11, Folder 958)
    - Grants/fundraising - Chicago Resource Center, 1996; 118110 (Box 11, Folder 959)
    - Grants/fundraising - City of New York - Neighborhood Tourism, 1996; 118109 (Box 11, Folder 960)
    - Grants/fundraising - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1996; 118108 (Box 11, Folder 961)
    - Grants/fundraising - Experimental Television Center, Ltd., 1996; 118107 (Box 11, Folder 962)
    - Grants/fundraising - Ford Foundation, 1996; 118106 (Box 11, Folder 963)
    - Grants/fundraising - Funding Exchange, 1996; 118105 (Box 11, Folder 964)
    - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts, 1996; 118104 (Box 11, Folder 965)
    - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1996; 118103 (Box 11, Folder 966)
    - Grants/fundraising - New York Community Trust grant correspondence, 1995-1996; 118102 (Box 11, Folder 967)
    - Grants/fundraising - New York Community Trust newsletter, 1996; 118101 (Box 11, Folder 968)
    - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts, 1996; 118100 (Box 11, Folder 969)
    - Grants/fundraising - North Star Fund, 1996; 118099 (Box 11, Folder 970)
    - Grants/fundraising - Office of the Manhattan Borough President correspondence, 1996; 118098 (Box 11, Folder 968)
    - Grants/fundraising - Open Meadows correspondence, 1996-1998; 118097 (Box 11, Folder 971)
    - Grants/fundraising - Playboy Foundation, 1996; 118096 (Box 11, Folder 972)
    - Grants/fundraising - Playboy Foundation, 1996; 118095 (Box 11, Folder 973)
    - Grants/fundraising - Paul Rapoport Foundation, 1996; 118094 (Box 11, Folder 974)
    - Grants/fundraising - Samuel Rubin Foundation, 1996; 118093 (Box 11, Folder 975)
    - Grants/fundraising - Stonewall Foundation, 1996; 118092 (Box 11, Folder 976)
    - Grants/fundraising - Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program, 1996; 118091 (Box 11, Folder 977)
    - Grants/fundraising - Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, 1996; 118090 (Box 11, Folder 978)
    - Grants/fundraising - Other sources of support, 1996; 118089 (Box 11, Folder 979)
- SERIES XI: 1997, 117751
  This series contains materials pertaining to the 11th year of the Festival.
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files, 118047
    - Expenses - Budgets, 1997; 118086 (Box 11, Folder 980)
    - Expenses - Bulk mail statements, 1997; 118085 (Box 11, Folder 981)
    - Expenses - Checkbooks, 1997; 118084 (Box 11, Folder 982)
    - Expenses - Checks, 1997; 118083 (Box 11, Folder 983)
    - Expenses - Distribution, 1997; 118082 (Box 11, Folder 984)
    - Expenses - Federal Express, 1997; 118081 (Box 11, Folder 985)
    - Expenses - Fleet Bank, 1997; 118080 (Box 11, Folder 986)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - touring programs and misc., 1997; 118079 (Box 11, Folder 987)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - May-June, 1997; 118078 (Box 11, Folder 988)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - July-August, 1997; 118077 (Box 11, Folder 989)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - September-October, 1997; 118076 (Box 11, Folder 990)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts - November-December, 1997; 118075 (Box 11, Folder 991)
    - Expenses - National Westminster Bank, 1997; 118074 (Box 11, Folder 992)
    - Expenses - Petty cash envelope, 1997; 118073 (Box 11, Folder 993)
    - Expenses - Pitney Bowes, 1997; 118072 (Box 11, Folder 994)
    - Expenses - Revenue, expenses, salaries, 1997; 118071 (Box 11, Folder 995)
    - Festival statements - Call for film/media works, 1997; 118070 (Box 11, Folder 996)
    - Festival statements - Press releases, 1997; 118069 (Box 11, Folder 997)
    - Hospitality - Festival pass information, 1997; 118068 (Box 11, Folder 998)
    - Hospitality - Press accreditation, 1997; 118067 (Box 11, Folder 999)
    - Mailing list - Address labels, 1997; 118066 (Box 11, Folder 1000)
    - Mailing list - To be added, 1997; 118065 (Box 11, Folder 1001)
    - Notes - Installations, 1997; 118064 (Box 11, Folder 1002)
    - Notes - Minutes from Board of Directors meetings, 1997; 118063 (Box 11, Folder 1003)
    - Notes - Notepad with memos, 1997; 118062 (Box 11, Folder 1004)
    - Notes - Phone messages, 1997; 118061 (Box 11, Folder 1005)
    - Notes - Venue scouting, 1997; 118060 (Box 11, Folder 1006)
    - Organizational - Committee information, 1997; 118059 (Box 11, Folder 1007)
    - Organizational - Corporate development, 1997; 118058 (Box 11, Folder 1008)
    - Organizational - Internship/staff list, 1997; 118057 (Box 11, Folder 1009)
    - Postal - Envelopes, 1997; 118056 (Box 11, Folder 1010)
    - Postal - Postage/delivery materials, 1997; 118055 (Box 11, Folder 1011)
    - Programming - Notes, 1997; 118054 (Box 11, Folder 1012)
    - Programming - Party schedule, 1997; 118053 (Box 11, Folder 1013)
    - Programming - Program guide, 1997; 118052 (Box 11, Folder 1014)
    - Programming - Program guide - mock-up, with correspondence and invoice from designer David Pace, 1997; 118051 (Box 11, Folder 1015)
    - Programming - Program listings, 1997; 118050 (Box 11, Folder 1016)
    - Programming - Program listings for catalog, 1997; 118049 (Box 11, Folder 1017)
    - Programming - Selection process, films listed by ranking, 1997; 118048 (Box 11, Folder 1018)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence, 118031
    - Correspondence from filmmakers and film/arts organizations, A-M, 1997; 118046 (Box 12, Folder 1019)
    - Correspondence from filmmakers and film/arts organizations, N-Z, 1997; 118045 (Box 12, Folder 1020)
    - Correspondence from Festival re: viewing copies of works, 1997; 118044 (Box 12, Folder 1021)
    - Rejection letters, 1997; 118043 (Box 12, Folder 1022)
    - Artists' Space, 1997; 118042 (Box 12, Folder 1023)
    - Cinema Village, 1997; 118041 (Box 12, Folder 1024)
    - Downtown Arts Festival, 1997; 118040 (Box 12, Folder 1025)
    - Free Speech TV, 1997; 118039 (Box 12, Folder 1026)
    - Hubbard, Jim, 1997; 118038 (Box 12, Folder 1027)
    - Roy, Rajendra, 1997; 118037 (Box 12, Folder 1028)
    - Distribution and mailing, 1997; 118036 (Box 12, Folder 1029)
    - Hospitality, 1997; 118035 (Box 12, Folder 1030)
    - Interns/volunteers, 1997; 118034 (Box 12, Folder 1031)
    - Press, 1997; 118033 (Box 12, Folder 1032)
    - Public relations, 1997; 118032 (Box 12, Folder 1033)
  - Subseries C: Entry Forms/Press Kits, 117992
    - Entry forms - Boywhore program, 1997; 118030 (Box 12, Folder 1034)
    - Entry forms - Closing Night featuring Tribe 8 program, 1997; 118029 (Box 12, Folder 1035)
    - Entry forms - Corazon: Lives of Quiet Desperation program, 1997; 118028 (Box 12, Folder 1036)
    - Entry forms - Cut program, 1997; 118027 (Box 12, Folder 1037)
    - Entry forms - De Profundis program, 1997; 118026 (Box 12, Folder 1038)
    - Entry forms - Dickplay program, 1997; 118025 (Box 12, Folder 1039)
    - Entry forms - Digitize Art! program, 1997; 118024 (Box 12, Folder 1040)
    - Entry forms - Documentado: Five Years of Mix Brasil program, 1997; 118023 (Box 12, Folder 1041)
    - Entry forms - Dollywood program, 1997; 118022 (Box 12, Folder 1042)
    - Entry forms - Drive program, 1997; 118021 (Box 12, Folder 1043)
    - Entry forms - Ethereal program, 1997; 118020 (Box 12, Folder 1044)
    - Entry forms - Funk program, 1997; 118019 (Box 12, Folder 1045)
    - Entry forms - Gong! program, 1997; 118018 (Box 12, Folder 1046)
    - Entry forms - I Only Have Eyes for You program, 1997; 118017 (Box 12, Folder 1047)
    - Entry forms - The Inconsistency of Memory program, 1997; 118016 (Box 12, Folder 1048)
    - Entry forms - Jack program, 1997; 118015 (Box 12, Folder 1049)
    - Entry forms - Lesbian Cyberspace Biography program, 1997; 118014 (Box 12, Folder 1050)
    - Entry forms - Melondrama program, 1997; 118013 (Box 12, Folder 1051)
    - Entry forms - Mixmaster program, 1997; 118012 (Box 12, Folder 1052)
    - Entry forms - Ooze program, 1997; 118011 (Box 12, Folder 1053)
    - Entry forms - Opening Night program, 1997; 118010 (Box 12, Folder 1054)
    - Entry forms - Platinum program, 1997; 118009 (Box 12, Folder 1055)
    - Entry forms - Queer(s)punk program, 1997; 118008 (Box 12, Folder 1056)
    - Entry forms - Raw program, 1997; 118007 (Box 12, Folder 1057)
    - Entry forms - Relative program, 1997; 118006 (Box 12, Folder 1058)
    - Entry forms - Retrovision program, 1997; 118005 (Box 12, Folder 1059)
    - Entry forms - Riot Grrrandmas program, 1997; 118004 (Box 12, Folder 1060)
    - Entry forms - Scared Stiff program, 1997; 118003 (Box 12, Folder 1061)
    - Entry forms - Spread program, 1997; 118002 (Box 12, Folder 1062)
    - Entry forms - To Catch a Glimpse program, 1997; 118001 (Box 12, Folder 1063)
    - Entry forms - Wig program, 1997; 118000 (Box 12, Folder 1064)
    - Entry forms - Guest curators' programs, 1997; 117999 (Box 12, Folder 1065)
    - Entry forms - Program proposals, 1997; 117998 (Box 12, Folder 1066)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by entry number, #1-42, 1997; 117997 (Box 12, Folder 1067)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by entry number, #43-85, 1997; 117996 (Box 12, Folder 1068)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by entry number, #86-129, 1997; 117995 (Box 12, Folder 1069)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by entry number, #130-168, 1997; 117994 (Box 12, Folder 1070)
    - Press kit - Shawna Dempsey and Lori Millan, 1997; 117993 (Box 12, Folder 1071)
  - Subseries D: Electronic Database, 117990
    - Database (.fp3 file, 487 kb)(see archivist for access), 1997; 117991 (Box 12, Folder 1072)
  - Subseries E: Press/Promotion/Posters (see also Oversize/Mapcase series), 117977
    - The Advocate - Mix ad, 1997; 117989 (Box 12, Folder 1073)
    - HX - Mix mention in Homo Musts, Mix ad, 1997; 117988 (Box 12, Folder 1074)
    - HX - Mix article in "The Reel Thing" section, mention in Homo Musts, 1997; 117987 (Box 12, Folder 1075)
    - Indiewire - Ed Halter article on Mix, 1997; 117986 (Box 12, Folder 1076)
    - Knitting Factory Knotes - Mix 97 schedule, 1997; 117985 (Box 12, Folder 1077)
    - New York - Mix mention in Film listings, 1997; 117984 (Box 12, Folder 1079)
    - New York Times - Mix mention in Film listings, 1997; 117983 (Box 12, Folder 1081)
    - Simon Says - Mix mention, 1997; 117982 (Box 12, Folder 1082)
    - Time Out New York - Bruce LaBruce article, 1997; 117981 (Box 12, Folder 1083)
    - Time Out New York - Mix mentions in Film Alternatives + Revivals and Gay + Lesbian sections, 1997; 117980 (Box 12, Folder 1084)
    - Time Out New York - Mix mentions in Film Alternatives + Revivals and Gay + Lesbian sections, 1997; 117979 (Box 12, Folder 1085)
    - Mix 97 "Shoot Art" postcard, 1997; 117978 (Box 12, Folder 1087)
  - Subseries F: Special Programs (see also Oversize series), 117968
    - Bates College touring program - Correspondence, program listing, invoices, 1997; 117976 (Box 12, Folder 1089)
    - Cafe con Leche - Flyers for Mix 97 benefit, 1997; 117975 (Box 12, Folder 1090)
    - Latin Boys Go to Hell/Fresh Fish, 1997; 117974 (Box 12, Folder 1091)
    - Mix Brasil - Pamphlets, 1997; 117973 (Box 12, Folder 1092)
    - Mix Brasil - Program guide, 1997; 117972 (Box 12, Folder 1093)
    - Mix Mexico - Program guide, 1997; 117971 (Box 12, Folder 1095)
    - Paperveins: Prosthetic Houses installation, 1997; 117970 (Box 12, Folder 1096)
    - Tribe 8 and Pansy Division - Press release and press kits, 1997; 117969 (Box 12, Folder 1098)
  - Subseries G: Media, 117785
    - Title: [1.]--Callback [2.]--Too Much Lipstick, Screened: 1997; 117967 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0891)
      Old number: 97-001, 19252
      Director: Hunt, Sarah
    - Title: The Barry Z Story, Screened: 1997; 117966 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0892)
      Old number: 97-002
      Director: Kapp, Matt
      Distributor: distributed by: National Video Industries, Inc.
    - Title: In Love With Happiness, Screened: 1997; 117965 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0893)
      Old number: 97-004
      Director: Best, Patricia
    - Title: Heads or Tails, Screened: 1997; 117964 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0894)
      Old number: 97-006
      Director: Selditch, Michael
    - Title: DeAundra Peek's Mysterious Ways, Screened: 1997; 117963 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0895)
      Old number: 97-007
      Director: Richards, Dick
    - Title: Collette and Chantelle, Screened: 1997; 117962 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0896)
      Old number: 97-010
      Director: O'Keefe, Gary
    - Title: The Booby Trap, Screened: 1997; 117961 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0897)
      Old number: 97-011
      Director: Haug, Kate
    - Title: Pass, Screened: 1997; 117960 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0898)
      Old number: 97-013
    - Title: Female Bidentity: Women Telling It Like It Is, Screened: 1997; 117959 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0899)
      Old number: 97-014
      Director: Hardacker, Jennifer
    - Title: Vanilla Lament, Screened: 1997; 117958 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0900)
      Director: Crouch, Catherine
    - Title: Snow White Walk, Screened: 1997; 117957 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0901)
      Old number: 97-016
      Director: Hall, Elizabeth
    - Title: Outta The Blue, Screened: 1997; 117956 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0902)
      Old number: 97-017
      Director: Saalfield, Catherine and Hope, Melanie
    - Title: Phi-Brite, Screened: 1997; 117955 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0903)
      Old number: 97-018
      Director: Koone, Jeff
    - Title: Once Upon A Time For The Children, Screened: 1997; 117954 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0904)
      Old number: 97-019
      Director: Sloan, Tamela
    - Title: The Unveiling, Screened: 1997; 117953 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0905)
      Old number: 97-020, 5382 #2
      Director: Evans, Rodney
    - Title: L'abandon, Screened: 1997; 117952 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0906)
      Old number: 97-021
      Duration: 16 minutes
    - Title: Inflorescentia, Screened: 1997; 117951 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0907)
      Old number: 97-022
      Director: Gabriele, Caroline
    - Title: Monday Morning, Screened: 1997; 117950 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0908)
      Old number: 97-023
      Director: Henry, Kyle
    - Title: [Untitled], Screened: 1997; 117949 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0909)
      Old number: 97-024
    - Title: Pretty Mean, Screened: 1997; 117948 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0910)
      Old number: 97-025
      Director: Cline, Robin
    - Title: Heart's Desire, Screened: 1997; 117947 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0911)
      Old number: 97-027
      Director: Mathieu, Betsy
    - Title: Between The Lines, Screened: 1997; 117946 (Box 130, Folder ID: 143.0912)
      Old number: 97-029
      Director: Constantinou, Sophie
    - Title: [1.]--More, Bigger, Better, Faster [2.]--Astropimpin' 43 Part I The Sequel- Trailer Trash (a) [3.]--Astropimpin' 43 Part I The Sequel- Trailer Trash (b), Screened: 1997; 117945 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0913)
      Old number: 97-032
      Director: Jones, Bambi and Lucki Jenkins
      Distributor: distributed by: Skylark Productions
    - Title: 1919, Screened: 1997; 117944 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0914)
      Old number: 97-033
      Director: Gonick, Noam
    - Title: "Law of Desire" from, Clit-o-Matic: The Adventures of White Trash Girl! Episode #2, Screened: 1997; 117943 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0915)
      Old number: 97-034
      Director: Reeder, Jennifer
    - Title: Peep, Screened: 1997; 117942 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0916)
      Old number: 97-035
      Director: Rekow, Leanne
      Duration: 7 minutes
    - Title: Swing, Screened: 1997; 117941 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0917)
      Old number: 97-036
    - Title: Coming To Her Senses: [1.]-- Narcissus [2.]-- Tiny Bubbles [3.]-- The Pickup [4.]-- This Missing You [5.]-- Angustia [6.]-- Bright and Dark, Screened: 1997; 117940 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0918)
      Old number: 97-037
      Director: [1.]-- Pietrobruno, Ileana [2.]-- Myers, Bo [3.]-- McPherson, Seanna [4.]-- Daniel, Mary [5.]-- Morgado, Claudia [6.]-- Epp, Ellie
    - Title: Groove On A Stanley Knife, Screened: 1997; 117939 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0919)
      Old number: 97-039
      Director: Krishnan, Tinge and Beth Kotler
    - Title: Front Room, Screened: 1997; 117938 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0920)
      Old number: 97-041
    - Title: Put Your Hands on Your Head, Screened: 1997; 117937 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0921)
      Old number: 97-042
    - Title: In Living Memory, Screened: 1997; 117936 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0922)
      Old number: 97-043
      Director: Gottlieb, Amy
    - Title: Bent TV Festival Tape: [1.]--Flexing the Triple Take (Drag Kings at HMI) [2.]--Sammy's Music Video [3.]--Bubbles Video [4.]--I Found My Rainbow, Screened: 1997; 117935 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0923)
      Old number: 97-047
      Director: [1.]-- Rusty [2.]-- Sammy Rivera Jr. [3.]-- Danitzia Pavlovich [4.]-- Rusty
    - Title: What Are You Looking For? Two Things That Go Together, Screened: 1997; 117934 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0924)
      Old number: 97-049
      Director: Bickart, Barbara
    - Title: The Boys of Cellblock Q, Screened: 1997; 117933 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0925)
      Old number: 97-050
      Director: Daniels, Alan
      Distributor: distributed by: Greenwood/Cooper Homevideo, A Division of Alluvial Entertainment, Inc.
    - Title: Sole, rope, other, Screened: 1997; 117932 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0926)
      Old number: 97-051
      Director: Hamburger, Ofer
    - Title: Dim, Screened: 1997; 117931 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0927)
      Old number: 97-052
      Director: Ranieri, Antonio
    - Title: Still Life, Screened: 1997; 117930 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0928)
      Old number: 97-055
      Director: Regan, Francis or [Beauvais, Yann]
    - Title: Good Citizen: Betty Baker, Screened: 1997; 117929 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0929)
      Old number: 97-056
      Director: Dempsey, Shawna and Millan, Lorri
    - Title: Tainted, Screened: 1997; 117928 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0930)
      Old number: 97-057
    - Title: Forever, Screened: 1997; 117927 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0931)
      Old number: 97-058
    - Title: Fistfull, Screened: 1997; 117926 (Box 131, Folder ID: 143.0932)
      Old number: 97-059
      Director: Swenson, Laurel
    - Title: Everybody Loves Nothing (Empathic Exercizes), Screened: 1997; 117925 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0933)
      Old number: 97-060
      Director: Reinke, Steve
    - Title: [1.]-- Condola [2.]--The Sad Story of a Gay Skater, Screened: 1997; 117924 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0934)
      Old number: 97-061
      Director: Wells, Jonathan and Geoffrey Topham
    - Title: [1.]--Emission [2.]--Shimmer, Screened: 1997; 117923 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0935)
      Old number: 97-062
    - Title: Your Mother Wears Combat Boots, Screened: 1997; 117922 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0936)
      Old number: 97-063
    - Title: Spanking Marsha, Screened: 1997; 117921 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0937)
      Old number: 97-064
      Director: Calvert, Melodie and Bonita Makuch
    - Title: Blending Milk and Water: Sex In the New World, Screened: 1997; 117920 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0938)
      Old number: 97-065
      Director: Wong, Paul
    - Title: [1.]--Aberrant Motion #1 [2.]--Aberrant Motion #4: Face Story, Stagger Stories [3.]--Twala, Screened: 1997; 117919 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0939)
      Old number: 97-066
    - Title: Not Simply a Wedding Banquet, Screened: 1997; 117918 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0940)
      Old number: 97-067
      Director: Chen, Mickey and Ming-Hsiu (Mia) Chen
    - Title: Faggots are for Burning, Screened: 1997; 117917 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0941)
      Old number: 97-068
      Director: McKay, Barry
    - Title: Top of the World, Screened: 1997; 117916 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0942)
      Old number: 97-069
      Director: Goodman, Rosser
      Distributor: distributed by: KGB Films
    - Title: Beauty Before Age, Screened: 1997; 117915 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0943)
      Old number: 97-070
    - Title: Julpari, Screened: 1997; 117914 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0944)
      Old number: 97-071
      Director: Khurana, Swati and Leith Gill Murgai
    - Title: Blue Boy, Screened: 1997; 117913 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0945)
      Old number: 97-072
      Distributor: additional credits: USC-Cinema
    - Title: Sniff, Screened: 1997; 117912 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0946)
      Old number: 97-073
      Director: Ma, Ming-Yuen
    - Title: Neverness, Screened: 1997; 117911 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0947)
      Old number: 97-074
      Director: Hourihan, Catherine
    - Title: Nana, George and Me, Screened: 1997; 117910 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0948)
      Old number: 97-075
      Director: Balass, Joe
    - Title: The Devil Won't Let Me Sleep, Screened: 1997; 117909 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0949)
      Old number: 97-076
    - Title: Fission, Screened: 1997; 117908 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0950)
      Old number: 97-077
      Director: Fan, Victor
    - Title: Galaxy Girls, Screened: 1997; 117907 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0951)
      Old number: 97-078
    - Title: Soulsucka, Screened: 1997; 117906 (Box 42, Folder ID: 143.0952)
      Old number: 97-079
      Director: Zeidler, Christina
    - Title: Dykes on Ice, Screened: 1997; 117905 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0953)
      Old number: 97-081
      Distributor: distributed by: Amsterdam or Bust Productions
    - Title: La memoire de l'eau, Screened: 1997; 117904 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0954)
      Old number: 97-082
      Director: Jean, Rodrigue
    - Title: Shift, Screened: 1997; 117903 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0955)
      Old number: 97-084, 97-085
      Director: Forrest, Niki
    - Title: Tango Lesbiango, Screened: 1997; 117902 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0956)
      Old number: 97-087
      Director: Cook, Susana
    - Title: Karen Black Like Me, Screened: 1997; 117901 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0957)
      Old number: 97-088
      Director: Briggs, David
    - Title: The Fatboy Chronicles, Part Two: The Boy with A Bugle, Screened: 1997; 117900 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0958)
      Old number: 97-089
      Director: Broussard, Rene
    - Title: Don't Run, Johnny, Screened: 1997; 117899 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0959)
      Old number: 97-091
      Director: Brown, Tom
      Distributor: distributed by: Bugsby Films
    - Title: Recipes for Babyfood, Screened: 1997; 117898 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0960)
      Old number: 97-092
      Director: Lazar, Alan Ari
    - Title: Pacific, Screened: 1997; 117897 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0961)
      Old number: 97-093
      Director: Rowley, Paul
    - Title: Coda, Screened: 1997; 117896 (Box 43, Folder ID: 143.0962)
      Old number: 97-094
      Director: Howard, Janet